

# ADRIAN TORREZ BELTRAN

# • DETAILS •

Morelia Mexico 4433354130 mineadriantorrez@gmail.com

# • LINKS •

<u>LinkedIn</u>

**GitHub** 

# • LANGUAGES •

Spanish

English

# • SKILLS •

HTML & CSS

PHP & JS

SQL

C#

C++ & Java

Unity & Unreal Engine

Office (Word, Excel, etc)

AutoCAD & 3D Maya

Paintig (Krita, Corel Draw, FlipaClip)

#### PROFILE

Video game developer with programming knowledge on C#, Unity and Unreal, also experienced with web design and development on HTML, CSS, JS and PHP as well with data base management, 3D modeling and GIT version control. Fast learner and easy adaptation to multiple environments.

# EDUCATION

Programming technician, High school CETis 120, Morelia, México.

August 2016 — July 2019

- C++ and Java knowledge.
- MySQL data base management.

Video game engineering, Universidad de Morelia, Morelia, México.

July 2019 — June 2023

- Unity and Unreal Engine video game development with POO C#.
- · Maya 3D modeling.
- Web design and development with HTML, CSS, PHP and JS.
- MySQL and MongoDB knowledge.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

System support at Alfa inmobiliaria e hipotecas, Morelia, Michoacán.

October 2019 — December 2021

- Web site support and update.
- Small designs on AutoCAD.
- · Document drafting and other office activities.

Cartographer at Instituto Nacional Electoral, Morelia, Michoacán.

November 2022 — June 2023

- Map update and digitization.
- Database information upload.
- Map archive management.

# INTERNSHIPS

Web site development at Preparatoria PREFECO, Morelia, México.

January 2022 — July 2022

- A website creation that allows at least 1,000 students to upload and control their psycho-pedagogical file.
- · Worked with a home-office methodology with a cloud workflow with GitHub

# COURSES

Mobile app development, Google Activate

November 2019

• Pixel Art course, Universidad de Morelia

November 2022